{
    "link": "https://tw.amazingtalker.com/blog/zh-tw/zh-jap/2228/", 
    "cards": [
        {"front": "日曜日\n(にちようび)", "back": "星期日"}, 
        {"front": "月曜日\n(げつようび)", "back": "星期一"}, 
        {"front": "火曜日\n(かようび)", "back": "星期二"}, 
        {"front": "水曜日\n(すいようび)", "back": "星期三"}, 
        {"front": "木曜日\n(もくようび)", "back": "星期四"}, 
        {"front": "金曜日\n(きんようび)", "back": "星期五"}, 
        {"front": "土曜日\n(どようび)", "back": "星期六"}, 
        {"front": "先週\n(せんしゅう)", "back": "上星期"}, 
        {"front": "今週\n(こんしゅう)", "back": "這星期"}, 
        {"front": "來週\n(らいしゅう)", "back": "下星期"}, 
        {"front": "再來週\n(さらいしゅう)", "back": "下下星期"}, 
        {"front": "今日\n(きょう)", "back": "今天"}, 
        {"front": "明日\n(あした)", "back": "明天"}, 
        {"front": "明後日\n(あさって)", "back": "後天"}, 
        {"front": "毎日\n(まいにち)", "back": "每天"}, 
        {"front": "毎週\n(まいしゅう)", "back": "每週"}, 
        {"front": "今日は何曜日ですか。", "back": "今天星期幾？"}, 
        {"front": "月曜日です。", "back": "星期一。"}
    ]
}